Hey, guys--
嘿  伙计们...
Wait! Let me tell them.
等等  我来跟他们讲
- Sure. - Joey's gonna be...
-好  -乔伊要...
...a celebrity guest on a game show.
在一个益智节目中做嘉宾了
Really? Which one?
真的  哪个节目
Fish. Seaweed.
鱼  海草
- A sunken ship. - Things you find in the ocean.
-沉船…  -海中之物…
- You're gonna be on Pyramid! - Yeah.
-你要上《智力金字塔》   -对
That was our favorite game show ever.
哦  那是我们最喜欢的益智节目了
Except for Match Game.
除了《匹配赛》以外
Or Win, Lose or Draw.
还有《输赢平》
What did I marry into?
瞧瞧我结的亲家
You guys wanna come
你们想明天
and watch me tape the show?
来看我录节目吗
Oh, we can't.
不行
We're throwing Phoebe a bachelorette party.
我们要给菲比开个婚前告别单身狂欢
Yeah. Sorry, boys, this ride's closing.
对喽  抱歉  兄弟们  此路不通
And Chandler and I have this stupid college alumni thing.
我和钱德勒要参加一个白痴校友聚会
I can't believe you get to meet Donny Osmond.
难以置信你要跟多尼·奥斯蒙德做节目
Seriously?
当真
Ross and I
罗斯和我
always wanted to be Donny and Marie.
以前总想学多尼和马瑞一样
You guys just keep getting cooler and cooler.
你们俩还越说越起劲儿了
Yeah, we used to perform
对  我们以前还在
for our family and friends.
家里和朋友面前表演过嘞
Oh, God, that's right. I blocked that out.
哦  没错  我还真给它忘了
I'm leaving you.
我要离开你了
《老友记》第十季第十一集 脱衣舞男之泪
《老友记》  第十季  第11集  脱衣舞男之泪
It's so weird to
又见到这些人
see all these people again.
太奇怪了
Oh, my God, look.
我的天啊  看
There's Jeffrey Klarik.
那是杰佛·克拉瑞
Who?
谁
He was roommates with John Rosoff.
约翰·卢瑟夫的室友
He went out with Andrea Tamborino.
他当时跟安卓·特布里诺拍拖
She dumped him for Michael Skloff.
她后来又跟迈克尔·斯克劳夫好上了
Did I go to this school?
我上的是这所学校吗
Hey, there's Missy Goldberg.
嘿  那是米西·戈尔伯格
You gotta remember her.
你肯定记得她
Sure. Nice.
当然  她很正点
Dude, you're married to my sister.
哥们儿  你可跟我老妹结了婚的
You're right.
你说的没错
By saying "nice,"
我夸她正点
I'm virtually licking her.
就是在舔她了
Hey, I hear she's single again.
嘿  我听说她又单身了
You think I should ask her out?
你说我是不是该跟她约会呢
Are you asking permission
你是不是想要
to break the pact?
打破君子协定
Yes, please.
是的  求你了
Hey. Hey, check out the fliers for the band.
瞧瞧乐队的传单
I made them on a Macintosh in the computer room.
我在机房的苹果机上做的
Awesome.
超赞的
The name really stands out.
名字还挺醒目的
Thanks to a little something called Helvetica Bold 24-point.
这多亏有了瑞士粗体24点
Man, we're gonna rock that Asian Student Union.
哥们儿  我们要在"亚学联"盖了
- Hey, guys. - Hey, Missy.
-嘿  伙计们   -嘿  米西
Our band is playing on Friday.
你知道吗  我们乐队星期五演出
Yeah, you should come check us out.
是啊  你该来看看
We're called Way/No Way.
我们的乐队名叫"行  还是不行"
- No way. - Way.
-不行   -行
- Great. I'll be there. - Fresh.
-好吧  到时见 -新鲜
- Boss. - Mint.
-老板. -薄荷.
- She's gone. - I know it.
-她走了   -我知道
I am totally gonna ask her out.
你知道吗  我一定要约到她
Dude, I was gonna ask her out.
哥们儿  我还想约她呢
I said it first, bro.
是我先说的  兄弟
Well, I thought it first, Homes.
那我还先想到的呢  老哥
Look, if you date--
听着  你要是约…
Wait! Wait! What are we doing?
等等  我们在干吗呢
What we have is too important
我们俩有太重要的事情
to mess it up over some girl.
可不能重色轻友反目成仇
I mean, we can get laid any time we want.
再说  天涯何处无芳草
Totally.
就是
I had sex in high schoo.
我高中就跟人上过床
Me too. I'm good at it.
我也是  我是情场高手
All right, I say we make a pact.
好吧  我们俩立个君子协定
Neither of us will go out with Missy Goldberg.
谁都不许跟米西·戈尔伯格约会
You got it.
一言为定
That's Missy Goldberg, Phoebe Cates
那么  现在我们就不能跟米西·戈尔伯格
and Molly Ringwald...
菲比·凯特
...who we can't go out with.
还有莫莉·里沃特约会了
Those are the pacts.
就是这么说的
And Sheena Easton.
哦  还有西娜·伊斯特
But we probably couldn't get her anyway.
反正我们也追不上她
Maybe not you.
或许你追不上吧
Well, I officially give you permission
好吧  我正式授权
to break the pact.
允许你打破君子协定
Thank you.
谢谢
All right. Here I go.
好  我要上啦
Hey, remember how scary it used to be
嘿  还记得上学时
going up to girls in college?
跟女孩说话都慌神吗
Your hands are shaking.
你的手在发抖呢
I know. And I can't stop sweating.
我知道  我还一个劲地冒汗
Five, four, three. Applause.
5  4  3  鼓掌
Yeah!
哦
Welcome.
欢迎大家
It is Soap Opera Week here on Pyramid.
这里是肥皂剧之周  《智力金字塔》
Let's meet our contestants.
来看看选手们
First, Gene Lester is a database specialist.
首先  是数据库专家金·拉斯特
He's gonna be playing with
他的搭档是
Days of Our Lives star
《我们的日子》剧中的明星
Joey Tribbiani.
乔伊·崔比安尼
I know it can be intimidating
嘿  我知道普通人跟名人
for regular people to be around celebrities...
在一起时都会紧张
...but relax.
不过没事儿
I'm just like you,
我跟你差不多
only better-looking and richer.
就是好看点儿  钱多点儿
She'll be playing with
…要跟《综合医院》剧中的
star of General Hospital, Leslie Charleson.
明星莱丝莉·查尔森搭档
Welcome, everybody. Good luck to all of you.
欢迎大家  祝各位好运
Let's play Pyramid.
我们开始玩《智力金字塔》  好吗
All right? Now, we flipped a coin
我们在节目开始之前
before the show.
已经抛过硬币了
Gene, you won the toss, so you'll start.
金  你猜对硬币    你先开始
Which category would you like?
你喜欢什么类型
I will take "You Crossed the Line."
我选择"你越线了"
"You Crossed the Line." Joey...
"你越线了"  乔伊
...describe for Gene these things that have lines.
你给金描述那些有线条的东西
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please.
限时20秒
Ready? Go.
预备  开始
SUPERMARKET:超市
SUPERMARKET:超市
Okay, it's a store like a supermarket.
象超市一样的商店...
I see what I did there.
我知道犯规了
Okay, okay. I'm writing in my....
好吧  好吧  我写…
Diary.
日记
No, more like a notebook.
不是  差不多接近笔记本
BLUEPRINT:蓝图
BLUEPRINT:蓝图
If I'm building a house, the plan...
要是我建所房子  设计图
...isn't called a "shmooprint" ....
不是叫什穆图…
I can't do that either?
带个"图"字都不行
FOOTBALLFIELD:足球场
FOOTBALLFIELD:足球场
In high school,
在高中
I once had sex with a girl
有一次我跟个女孩做爱
right in the middle of the...?
就在某地中央
Cafeteria?
自助餐厅
Yeah, but they're not looking for that.
是有过那么一次  但那不是他们要的那个词
Thank you so much for this.
真的太感谢你们为此做的一切
You like it?
哦  你喜欢吗
Oh, my God, it's all so elegant.
我的天啊   还挺高雅的呢
When's the dirty stuff starting?
什么时候开始来点儿刺激的
What?
什么
You know.
你知道的
The strippers and the guys dancing...
脱衣舞啦  男子艳舞啦
...and, you know, pee-pees flying about.
小便四处飞散
Pheebs, l....
菲比  我…
There isn't gonna be any "flying about."
今天没有什么"四处飞散"
We actually thought we were a little too mature
事实上  我们觉得我们老大不小的了
for stuff like that.
还玩这些
Oh, okay.
哦  好吧
I see what you're doing. That's fine.
我知道你们在干吗  好的
This is all there is. Just tea. Okay.
今天就是个茶话会  好的
Raunchy.
好淫荡啊
Seriously, Pheebs,
真的  菲比
it's not gonna be that kind of a party.
这不是那种狂欢
Really? So this is...?
真的  这就是
This is my big sendoff into married life?
我的婚前单身告别会
Rachel, this is the only bachelorette party I'm ever gonna have.
瑞秋  我可就只有这一次单身告别会啊
I've got a big wad of ones in my purse.
我钱包里装了好多一块的钱呢
Really? I mean, really? It's just tea?
真的  今天就只是茶话会
No.
当然不是了
Phoebe, of course there's more.
菲比  还有别的呢
Okay.
好吧
I mean, let me just go talk to Monica...
我是说  我去问问莫妮卡
...and get an ETA on the pee-pees.
看什么时候上艳舞啊
Now, Gene, I must remind you,
现在  金  我要提醒你
you need all six of these to stay in the game.
必须答对6题才能留下来
Describe for Joey
给乔伊描述
"things you find in your refrigerator."
"冰箱里的物品"
They might as well just give us the points.
我看这简直是给我们送分啊
Give me 20 seconds on the clock.
限时20秒
Ready? Go.
预备  开始
You put this in your coffee.
CREAM:奶油
A spoon. Your hands. Your face.
勺子  手  脸
It's white.
它是白色的
Paper. Snow. A ghost!
纸  雪  鬼
It's heavier than milk.
它比牛奶重
A rock. A dog. The Earth.
石头  狗  地球
Pass.
过
MAYONNAISE:蛋黄酱
MAYONNAISE:蛋黄酱
You put it on a sandwich.
你往三明治上放的东西
Salami. Anchovies. Jam.
萨拉米香肠  凤尾鱼  果酱
It's white.
白色的
Paper. Snow. A ghost!
纸  雪  鬼
It's made from eggs.
它使用鸡蛋做的
Chickens?
小鸡
Pass.
过
KETCHUP:调味蕃茄酱
KETCHUP:调味蕃茄酱
You put this on a hamburger.
你往汉堡包上放的东西
Ketchup! Relish!
番茄酱  辣酱
SODA: 苏打水
SODA: 苏打水
Stop!
停
Oh, time's up. Well,
哦  时间到
Joey, you were...
乔伊  你…
...almost on a roll there. Gene...
差点儿就上榜了  金...
...you'll have a chance to go to the Winner's Circle,
你下半场还可能有机会进入决胜圈的
but now...
但是现在
...Henrietta,
亨瑞达
you're going to the Winner's Circle to try your luck for $ 10,000...
你待会儿将进入决胜圈一试运气赢取一万美金
...right after this. Don't go away.
广告时间  不要走开
And we're out.
停
Oh, so we didn't win.
我们没赢又怎样呢
But it's fun to play the game, right?
乐在其中也不错  对吧
I got a kid starting college.
我有个孩子刚上大学
I have to get surgery on my knee.
我的膝盖要做手术
You just lost me 10 grand.
你刚刚让我损失一万美金
Oh, wow.
喔
I'm so sorry.
抱歉
Okay, I promise, we'll do better next time.
我保证下一轮我们发挥好一点
Well, I will,
我会发挥好一些
because I won't be playing with you.
因为我不会跟你搭档了
Hey, some of those are pretty hard.
你要知道  有些题目也太难了点
Like, why would there be a ghost in my fridge?
例如我的冰箱里怎么会有鬼的
Yeah.
是啊
- So Saturday night? - I'd love to.
-那么  星期六晚上   -我很愿意
Great.
太好了
So how come it took you so long to ask me out?
你怎么这么长时间才约我
Oh, well, this is gonna sound kind of silly...
呃  这听起来有些愚蠢  但是...
...but do you remember my roommate, Chandler Bing?
你还记得我的室友 钱德勒·宾
Sure. He was in your "band."
当然  他在你的"乐队"里
It's been 16 years,
已经16年了
but the air quotes still hurt.
不过那个引号还是挺伤人的
Sorry.
对不起
That's okay. Anyway....
没关系
Well, he and I both really liked you a lot...
总之  我们那时都很喜欢你
...but we didn't want it
但是我们又不想
to jeopardize our friendship,
为此伤友谊
so we made a pact...
所以我们约定
...that neither of us could ask you out.
谁也不能跟你约会
- Really? - Yeah, why?
-真的   -是啊  怎么了
Well, Chandler and I used to make out.
呃  我和钱德勒曾经亲热啊
A lot.
而且经常
- You did? - Yeah.
-是吗   -对呀
We'd go to the science lab after-hours.
我们常在下课后到实验室去
And on my turf?!
还在我的地盘上
Hey, where is this guy?
嘿  那家伙还没来
It's been over an hour.
都一个多小时了
He's coming from Jersey.
他要从新泽西赶过来
He said he'd get here as fast as he could.
他说会尽快赶到的
- Who is it? - It's the police.
-谁呀   -警察
The police!
是警察
That's right. It's Officer Goodbody.
没错  是"好身材"警官
What's the matter, officer?
出什么事啦  警官
Has someone been bad?
是不是有人调皮了
That's a lot of stairs.
这么多楼梯
Boy.
老天
You should warn people there's no elevator.
你们应该告诉人家这栋楼没电梯
I should not have had that Mexican food for lunch.
我午饭不该吃墨西哥菜
Are you gonna be okay, Officer...?
你没事吧  警官…
Goodbody.
"好身材"
If you say so.
你非要那么说的话
So where's the young lady...
那么  哪位是
...who I am supposed to take downtown?
我要"逮捕"的年轻女士啊
Oh, God.
我的天啊
Somebody show me where to plug in my box...
谁告诉我在哪接我的录音机
...and we'll get this party started.
我们开始狂欢吧
- Over here? - Yeah.
-在这   -对啊
- All right. - Rachel?
-好吧  -瑞秋
- Yeah? - Are you kidding?
-啊   -呃  你是不是在开我的玩笑
We didn't know you wanted a stripper,
好吧  我们原来不知道你想要脱衣舞男
so we went to the phone book...
所以我们借助于电话簿
...and got the first name we could find.
找到第一个名字就打了过去
How old's your phone book?
你们的电话簿有多老了
Oh, my God,
我的天啊
this man is gonna get naked in my apartment.
这个男人要在我的公寓里脱光光
God, no.
上帝  不要
I don't wanna see him take his clothes off.
我可不想看他跳脱衣舞
Are you talking about me?
你是在说我吗
No.
不
I mean, obviously we wanna see you take your clothes off.
我是说  我们显然是要看你跳脱衣舞的
You big piece of eye candy.
你这个养眼的万人迷
Okay. Okay, ladies,
好的  女士们
can I have your attention, please?
请注意了
Oh, yeah.
哦  好
Did someone call for the long arm of the law?
有人呼唤法律的巨擘了吗
I should warn you,
我要警告你
I have a concealed weapon.
我有秘密武器呦
I hope you're familiar with this state's penal code.
我希望你们熟悉本州的刑法
Okay, okay. Enough teasing.
好了好了  玩笑开够了
Now for some pleasing.
现在该乐一乐了
She cringed.
她躲我
This is how I look when I'm turned-on.
我兴奋的时候  就是这样的
You were talking about me before.
你们刚才就是在说我
Look, I don't need this.
我可不需要这些
I'm out of here. Where's my hat?
我要走了  我的帽子呢
Look, I've been in this business for a long time.
我干这行已经很长时间了
Shocking.
骇人听闻
Now, if you'll just pay me my $300,
现在  你付我300块
I'll be on my way.
我这就走人
$300? Are you kidding?
300块  你开什么玩笑
That's okay. Let me get my checkbook.
没关系  我来拿支票
No. You're not gonna pay him.
不  你不用付他钱
He didn't do anything.
他什么也没干
Didn't do anything?
什么也没干
I took a bus all the way from Hoboken.
我大老远的从毫尔伯肯搭公交车赶来
I climbed, I don't know, like, a billion stairs.
我爬了  天知道的  上亿的台阶
And it's not like
这两样儿
I can take them two at a time.
我可不是能一次完成的
I don't care.
我不管
We're not paying you $300 for this.
我们才不会就为这个付给你300块钱
It's not my fault
那好  你那么保守
if you're too uptight to appreciate...
欣赏不了男性的身材和魅力
...the male form in all its glory.
这又不是我的错
Okay, I'm uptight.
哦  是  我保守
That's why I don't wanna watch a middle-aged guy...
所以我不想看个半大老头儿
...dance around in what I can only assume
穿一身我只能认为是
is a child's Halloween costume.
小孩万圣节的行头跳脱衣舞
I may have borrowed this from my nephew...
我也许是从我侄子那儿借的衣服
...but let me assure you,
但我担保衣服里头
what's underneath is all man.
可是货真价实的真男人
I'm sorry,
抱歉
did you say "all man" or "old man"?
你是说真男人还是老男人
You're mean.
你可真刻薄
- Look, officer-- Sir? - Damn it.
-瞧  警官…  -该死
Big surprise.
没想到吧
The hunk of beef has feelings.
大块头也会感情丰富
Applause.
鼓掌
Okay, Henrietta,
好  亨瑞达
Jack and Jill Went Up The Hill:儿歌
你选了"男人女人去山顶"（儿歌）
My friend Rachel has a kid.
我朋友瑞秋有个小孩
I totally know nursery rhymes.
我对儿歌很熟悉
Joey, describe these things associated
乔伊  描述以下
with the United States Congress.
跟美国国会有关的事物
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please.
限时20秒
Ready? Go.
预备  开始
LEGISLATURE:立法机构
LEGISLATURE:立法机构
Pass.
过
ROTUNDA:圆形大厅
ROTUNDA:圆形大厅
FILIBUSTER:在立法机构中采用阻碍策略
FILIBUSTER:在立法机构中采用阻碍策略
Pass.
过
ADDENDUM:附录
ADDENDUM:附录
- The thing hanging in your throat. - Uvula.
-你喉咙后面挂着的小东西   -悬雍垂
Then pass.
那过
JOINT SESSION:上下两议院的联席会议
JOINT SESSION:上下两议院的联席会议
Okay. Henrietta,
好了  亨瑞达
you didn't get all the points you needed...
你没有得到所需的分数
...so that means,
所以  那就意味着
Gene, you are going to the Winner's Circle to try for $ 10,000.
金  你将进入决胜圈来赢取一万美金
And you're gonna be going there with Joey Tribbiani.
而且你将与乔伊·崔比安尼一起搭档
You made out with Missy Goldberg?
你跟米西·戈尔伯格亲热过
How could you do that after you promised me?
你怎么能在向我保证过之后还这么做
Excuse me.
失陪一下
That didn't make us sound gay at all.
你那么说  让我们听起来一点不像同性恋
You broke the pact.
你违反了君子协定
Ross, that was 16 years ago.
罗斯  那是16年前的事了
That doesn't matter.
那也不行
We're talking about the foundation of our friendship.
现在说的是我们之间友谊的基础
I believe the foundation of our friendship was unfortunate hair.
我以为我们之间友谊的基础是难堪的发型
All right, look.
好吧  你看
If we're really gonna do this,
要是我们真的明算账的话
it's not like you never broke one of the pacts.
你也不是没干过违反君子协定的事
- I didn't. - Oh, really?
-我没有   -真的
- No. - Oh, really?
-没有   -真的
- No. - Adrienne Turner.
-没有   -艾德丽安·特娜
Yes?
在
- Hey, Adrienne. - Hey, Adrienne. Hey.
-嘿  艾德丽安  -嘿  艾德丽安  嘿
I never did anything with Adrienne Turner.
我从没跟艾德丽安·特娜搅和到一起
Oh, please.
哦  得了吧
And you knew how much I liked her.
你知道我有多喜欢他
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么
Really? Remember that party freshman year?
A真的  还记得大一那年圣诞节假期前一个星期
A week before Christmas vacation? I do.
那个大狂欢吗  我记得
You had some visitors.
当时有人来找你
I can't believe we're at a real college party.
难以置信我们在一个真的大学聚会上
I have to pee so bad.
我兴奋得直想尿尿
This is so awesome.
这可真棒
College guys are so cute.
大学男生好可爱
Hey, you've got a boyfriend.
嘿  你有男朋友了
I know.
我知道
Corey Haim:80年代知名青少年演员
不过要是有个象克瑞·哈姆那样的想亲我
I am so gonna let him.
我是不会拒绝的
Hey, look, there's Chandler.
看  那是钱德勒
That stupid friend of Ross'
罗斯的白痴朋友
who said I was fat.
说我胖的那个
You know, I've already lost four pounds.
你要知道  我都瘦掉4磅了
You can so totally tell.
就是  一眼就看得出来
I know!
我就知道
Well, let's see,
过去看看
maybe he knows where Ross is.
他可能知道罗斯在哪
Hey, how's it going?
嘿  怎么样
- Aren't you...? - Yeah, Rachel.
-你不是...  -对  瑞秋
And this is Ross' sister, Monica.
这是罗斯的妹妹  莫妮卡
We met at Thanksgiving.
我们感恩节见过
Right. So how you doing?
对  最近如何
Bitchen.
再好不过
- Hi, Monica. - Hi, Chandler.
-嗨  莫妮卡   -嗨  钱德勒
It's really nice to see you. Not!
见到你很高兴...才怪
Okay.
好吧
I'll see if I can find Ross.
我看看能不能找到罗斯
Oh, my God, Rach. Beanbag chairs.
哦我的天  瑞秋  充气椅
Do not let me sit in one of those.
千万别让我坐上去
We'll be here for days.
不然我坐那几天也不会起来
Listen, Adrienne,
听着  艾德丽安
you can't tell Chandler about this.
你可不能告诉钱德勒这件事
Oh, believe me, Ross,
哦  相信我  罗斯
I won't be telling anybody about this.
我不会告诉任何人的
Cool.
酷
I didn't know you knew about that.
我以为你不知道
Well, I did. And it hurt.
但是我知道了  我还很伤心
That's when I wrote the song "Betrayal in the Common Room."
所以我才写了《在休息室被背叛》那首歌
Man, I'm sorry.
嘿  对不起
Look, that was a long time ago.
好了  那都是陈年往事了
So I made out with Adrienne,
那  我跟艾德丽安亲热
and you made out with Missy.
而你跟米西亲热
Well, I guess we're even.
我看我们俩扯平了
We are even, right?
我们俩扯平了  对吧
One more thing.
还有一件事
I was so pissed at you that night,
那晚我特生你的气
I wanted to get back at you.
想报复你
So I thought,
所以我当时想
"Who does Ross like more than anybody?"
"谁是罗斯最喜欢的人呢"
What did you do to my mom?
你对我妈做了什么
Not her.
不是她
I am so drunk.
我可真醉了
That's weird.
那就怪了
I've had the same number of beers as you
我跟你喝的差不多
and don't feel anything.
怎么我一点没感觉
So you girls having fun?
你俩玩儿得愉快吗
For your information, ass-munch...
跟你说  好的不得了
...I've lost four pounds.
我瘦了4磅
Maybe even five with all the dancing.
没准儿跳完舞会瘦到5磅
- Somebody order a pizza? - Oh, that's me!
-有人定比萨饼了吗   -哦  是我
I am so not gonna do good on my SATs tomorrow.
我明天的入学考试算是没戏了
Well, maybe you could go to school here next year
那  明年也许你可以到我们这儿来上大学
and we could totally hang out.
我们可以一块玩玩
Oh, yeah. There's a plan.
哦  对  好主意
Why don't I just start taking my smart pills now.
那我干脆现在就吃点脑灵通得了
Well, maybe you could get in on a beauty scholarship.
没准儿你能拿到选美奖学金呢
What a line.
别骗人了
- So where are you applying to? - Well...
-那  你都申请了哪些学校   -唔..
You know,l think it's kind of really important
你知道  我觉着我要去的地方应该阳光明媚
that I go somewhere where there's sun.
这很重要  所以我想…
So I'm sort of-- Hey!
所以我想...嗨
I'm in college, and I'm in a band.
我是大学生  还是乐队成员
Yeah, okay.
那好吧
What's the matter?
怎么啦
You never saw
你们没见过
a 50-year-old stripper cry before?
五十岁的脱衣舞男哭吗
You know, it's fine.
好吧
We'll pay you.
我们付你钱还不行吗
No, no, you're right.
不不  你说得对
Who am I kidding?
我在开谁的玩笑
I should have hung up that breakaway jockstrap years ago.
早几年我就该挂起那逃脱三角绷带  不干了
What am I gonna do? I mean...
现在我该怎么办
...this has been my life for 32 years.
我是说  我干这个都32年了
Taking my clothes off in front of people is all I know.
我只会在人家面前脱衣服
No, wait, there's got to be something else that you can do.
不  等等  一定还有别的事你能做的
I mean, what skills do you have?
我是说  你还有什么技术吗
I don't know.
我不知道
I can make my pecs dance.
我能让我的胸肌跳舞
I can pick up a dollar bill with my butt cheeks.
我可以用屁股蛋儿夹起1美元
I can go to that special place inside me
而在我的内心深处
where I feel no shame.
并无羞愧之意
So maybe something in an office.
那你也许可以从政
Or you could-- You could teach stripping.
或者你可以教人跳脱衣舞
You know, share your gift. Pass the torch.
你知道吗  分享你的天赋  发扬光大
You know, actually, that's not a bad idea.
对呀  这主意不赖
I could do it out of my apartment.
我可以在我的公寓外头教
I don't think my mom would mind.
我想我妈不会介意的
There you go.
这下好啦
Okay. You think you're gonna be okay?
你感觉好一点了吧
- Yeah. Yeah. - Yeah.
-对  好点了 -好
This is so weird.
太奇怪了
You never know when it's gonna be
你永远不会知道什么时候
your last dance.
是你的最后一舞
And I didn't even get a chance to finish it.
而且我甚至都没能跳完最后一支舞
Finish it.
那你把它跳完吧
- What? - Your last dance. Do it for us.
-什么   -你的最后一次  给我们跳完吧
- Really? - Really?
-你当真   -你当真
Yeah. Yeah, he deserves to do
是的  他应该最后再做
the thing he loves one last time.
一次他喜爱的事
Okay. All right. Get ready, ladies.
好的  准备好了  女士们
Okay.
好了
Oh, this is so hot!
这可真让人兴奋
Oh, no, don't stop.
别  别停下来
Have to.
跳不动了
Welcome to the Winner's Circle.
欢迎来到决胜圈
Joey, Gene, you guys ready?
乔伊  金  你们准备好了吗
- Yeah. - Sure.
-好了   -当然
Okay. Give me 60 seconds on the clock, please.
好  限时60秒
Ready? Go.
预备  开始
TYPES OF TREES:树种
TYPES OF TREES:树种
Oak. Maple. Elm. Birch.
橡树  枫树  榆树  桦树
I don't know. Types of trees...?
我...我不知道  树种
SPANISH WORDS:西班牙单词
SPANISH WORDS:西班牙单词
Buenos dias. Enchilada. Por favor.
早安  玉米卷饼  请
Oh, I'm so sorry, I don't know any Spanish words.
哦  抱歉  西班牙单词我一个不认识
THINGS THAT BURN:可燃烧之物  有灼痛感之物
THINGS THAT BURN:可燃烧之物  有灼痛感之物
A match. A candle.
火柴  蜡烛
Things that go: when you put them out.
扑灭时发出"嗞"声的东西
A torch. A bonfire.
火炬  篝火
- Your pee. - Things that burn.
-哦  你的小便   -燃烧物
WHAT A DOG MIGHT SAY:狗狗会说什么
WHAT A DOG MIGHT SAY:狗狗会说什么
"I'd like to go for a walk."
我要去散散步
"Scratch my belly."
挠挠我的肚皮
Dude. Dude, I think you're losing it.
哥们儿  我觉得你说的太乱了
"I have fur." "I like to bark."
我有毛  我会吠叫
What a dog says.
哦  这狗说的好啊
PIZZA TOPPINGS:比萨饼料
PIZZA TOPPINGS:比萨饼料
- Pepperoni. - Pizza toppings!Next.
-意大利辣香肠  -比萨饼料  下一个
Cindy Crawford. Christie Brinkley.
辛迪·克劳馥  克莉斯蒂·布林克利
Heidi Klum. Claudia Schiffer.
海蒂·克劳姆  克劳迪娅·西佛
Christy Turlington. Kate Moss.
克莉斯蒂·特林顿  凯特·玛斯
Girls Chandler could never get?
钱德勒永远追不上的女孩
- Supermodels. - Where?
-超级名模   -哪儿
Hey. Where's Rachel?
嘿  瑞秋在哪
She and Phoebe took the stripper to the hospital.
她和菲比送脱衣舞男上医院了
Did you know Chandler kissed Rachel?
你知不知道钱德吻过瑞秋
What? When was this?
什么  什么时候
1987.
1987年
The weekend you guys visited me at school.
你们俩上学校找我去的那个周末
Oh, my God. That's wild.
我的天  那也太疯狂了
But it was, like, a million years ago.
是  不过那是很久以前的事了
- It doesn't matter. - It matters to me.
-没什么要紧的   -但那对我很要紧
Why?
为什么
Because the night you kissed Rachel...
因为你吻瑞秋的那晚
...was the night I kissed Rachel for the very first time.
也是我第一次吻瑞秋
You kissed her that night too?
你那晚也吻瑞秋了
Two guys in one night?
一晚上两个男人
Oh, I thought she became a slut
我还以为她整过鼻子以后
after she got her nose fixed.
才变得放荡了呢
Seriously, where did this happen?
说真的  你在哪儿吻的瑞秋
Okay...
是这样的
...after you told me she was passed out in our room...
你告诉我瑞秋在我们屋里睡了之后
...l went in there to make sure she was all right.
我进去看看她怎么样了
She was lying on my bed,
她躺在我床上
all buried in people's coats.
睡在一堆衣服下面
I went to kiss her on the forehead...
我过去想吻她的额头
...but it was so dark,
但屋里太暗
I accidentally got her lips.
我不小心亲到了她的嘴唇
I started to pull away,
我想离开
but then I felt her start to kiss me back.
但我觉得她也开始吻我
It was only for a second, but it was amazing.
那只有一瞬间但感觉太奇妙了
And now I find out that you kissed her first.
但是现在  我却发现你先吻了她
Wait, what bed did you say she was on?
等等  你刚才说她在哪张床上
Mine.
我床上
I'm sure I put her on my bed.
我记得很清楚我把她放到我床上的
No, she was definitely on my bed.
不对  她肯定是在我床上
Why would I kiss a girl and then put her on your bed?
我干吗吻完一个女孩后把她放到你床上
Well, then who was on my bed?
那当时我床上的是谁
Oh, oh, oh...
哦  哦  哦
No! No! No!
不  不  不
Yes!
是的
You were under the pile of coats?
你在那堆衣服下面
I was the pile of coats!
那堆衣服就是我
Oh, my God!
我的天啊
You were my midnight mystery kisser?!
你是我的午夜神秘接吻人
You were my first kiss with Rachel?!
你是我和瑞秋的初吻
You were my first kiss ever?!
你就是我这辈子的初吻
What did I marry into?!
瞧瞧我结的什么亲家
Crap!
完蛋了